export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "Anatomy",
    back:
      "The study of the structure of body parts and their relationships to one another ",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "Physiology",
    back:
      "the study of the function of the body and how body parts work and carry out their life-sustaining activities",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "Gross Anatomy",
    back:
      "the study of large body structures visible to the naked eye (ex. heart, lungs, and kidneys)",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "Regional Anatomy",
    back:
      "study of all of the structures (muscles, bones, blood vessels, nerves, etc.) in a particular region of the body, such as the abdomen or leg, are examined at the same time",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "Systemic Anatomy",
    back:
      "the study of large body structures visible to the naked eye (ex. heart, lungs, and kidneys)",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "Miscroscopic Anatomy",
    back: "the study of body structures that are not visible to the naked eye",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    front: "Cytology",
    back: "the study of the cells of the body",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    front: "Histology",
    back: "the study of the tissues of the body",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    front: "Dorsal Cavity",
    back:
      "protects the nervous system organs; two subdivisions: cranial cavity (brain) and vertebral/spinal cavity (spine)",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    front: "Cranial Cavity",
    back: "cavity inside the skull which encases the brain",
    mastered: false,
    frontflip: true
  }
];
